csc.gov.in 2019-12-07

# Welcome to CSC E-Governance Services India Limited

[**Home**](https://csc.gov.in/) __About CSC __CSC privacy policy

## CSC Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is an electronic record in the form of an Electronic Contract. This policy explains how the data on personal information is collected, stored and used when you visit the CSC Portal, to ensure that we provide relevant and timely services to you and improve your experience of the website. All the users are advised to read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting CSCs website you expressly give us consent to use & disclose your personal information in accordance with the Policy.

**Note:** This privacy policy is a legally binding document between you and CSC. Our privacy policy may change at any time without prior notification. To make sure that you are aware of any changes, kindly review the policy periodically. 

## General

At CSC, the privacy of our visitors/customers is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by CSC and how it is used.

We will not sell, share or rent your personal information to any 3rd party or use your email address/mobile number for unsolicited emails and/or SMS. Any emails and/or SMS sent by CSC will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services & products and this Privacy Policy. Periodically, we may share newsletters and general statistical information about CSC & its users. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

## Personal Information

Personal Information means and includes all information that can be linked to a specific individual or to identify any individual, such as name, address, mailing address, telephone number, email ID, credit card number, cardholder name, card expiration date, information about your mobile phone, DTH service, data card, electricity connection and any details that may have been voluntarily provide by the user in connection with availing any of the services on CSC. We do not sell or share any personally identifiable information volunteered on this portal to any third party (public/private). Any information provided to this portal will be protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

When you browse through CSC, we may collect information regarding the domain and host from which you access the internet, the Internet Protocol [IP] address of the computer or Internet service provider [ISP] you are using, and anonymous site statistical data.

## Use Of Personal Information

We use personal information to provide you with services & products you explicitly requested for, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot concerns, help promote safe services, collect money, measure consumer interest in our services, inform you about offers, products, services, updates, customize your experience, detect & protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions, etc. We also use your contact information to send you important communication and information related to CSC.

## Cookies

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. We and our partners use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit CSC portal, and this may include using cookies or similar technologies to identify your browser. No personal information will be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

## Links to Other Sites

Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. CSC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

## Security

CSC has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. We gather certain information about the Registered User, such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, domain name, browser type, operating system, the date and time of the visit and the pages visited. We make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting our site unless an attempt to damage the site has been detected.

## Consent

By continuing to use this website, you confirm that you have read, understood and agreed to this Privacy Policy and consent to us using your personal information as described.
